mocpages.com 2007-12-13

# MOCpages.com : Privacy policy

>   
>  We respect your privacy.  
> 
>
>> MOCpages.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting MOCpages.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**
>> 
>> What personal information about site visitors does MOCpages.com gather?
>> 
>>   * **Information you give us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. Examples. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests and communicating with you. 
>>   * **Automatic information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses MOCpages.com. Examples. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at MOCpages.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
>>   * **E-mail communications:** No one likes unsolicited e-mail. MOCpages will only send e-mail to confirm actions you take on our web site, to alert you to information about your account status, and to communicate with you about administrative issues. For example, account holders receive e-mail when a review is written on one of their creations. Another example: you can request a new password via e-mail if you've forgotten your password. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, you can adjust your notification preferences. 
>> 
What about cookies? 
>> 
>>   * Our cookies are simple numeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as tracking what reviews you have written, whose creations you have voted on, and which creations you like best. 
>>   * The Help portion of the tool bar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of MOCpages.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 
>> 
Does MOCpages.com share the information it receives?
>> 
>> Absolutely not. 
>> 
>>   * **No junk mail:** We hate unsolicited e-mail just as much as everyone else. We will never distribute, sell, or abuse your e-mail address. Period. As an account holder, your e-mail address is used as your account name only so that we can uniquely recognize you, and so that we can communicate with you. 
>>   * **Employees:** As we continue to develop, we may employ individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from our databases, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, or providing customer service. They would have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
>>   * **Protection of MOCpages.com and others:** If the situation were to arise, we would release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of MOCpages.com, our visitors, account holders, or others. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from visitors or account holders for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
>>   * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might need to go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 
>> 
Which information can I access?
>> 
>> MOCpages.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with MOCpages.com for the purpose of viewing or updating that information. You have freedom to update all of your account information, your pages, reviews you've written, votes you've cast, and more.  Examples
>> 
>> What choices do I have? 
>> 
>>   * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make an account or to take advantage of such MOCpages.com features as reviews, voting, or other features that may be released in the future. 
>>   * You can add or update certain information on pages throughout your account. When you update information, we do not keep a copy of the prior version. 
>>   * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your notification preferences. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of MOCpages.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.) 
>>   * The Help portion of the tool bar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use some important features if you do not use cookies. 
>>   * The following are some products that offer anonymous browsing. [www.anonymizer.com](http://www.anonymizer.com/), [www.IDzap.com](http://www.idzap.com/), [www.somebody.net](http://www.somebody.net/), and [www.zeroknowledge.com](http://www.zeroknowledge.com/). We cannot vouch for the effectiveness of any of these products. 
>>   * In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, [Site seeing on the Internet](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.html). 
>> 
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 
>> 
>> If you choose to visit MOCpages.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas. If you have any concern about privacy at MOCpages.com, please send us a thorough description to our support staff, and we will try to resolve it. 
>> 
>> Our web site changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected account holders. 
>> 
>> Related Practices and Information 
>> 
>>   * Conditions of Use
>>   * Help department
>> 
  
> 
>> 
>>   
>  **Information you give us**
>> 
>> You provide information when you search, browse, write reviews, rate creations, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when signing in); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; and employ other services, such as notification alerts. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, e-mail address, content of reviews, personal descriptions, or photographs. We also, obviously, store any of the information that you, as an account holder, choose to display on your pages, such as page titles, descriptions of your creations, links to pictures and links other sites. When you add photos to your pages, small copies of those photos (called "thumbnails") are stored on MOCpages.com. These thumbnails are only viewable via your pages. 
>> 
>>   
>  **Automatic information**
>> 
>> Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; name; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; MOCs you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our customer service. 
>> 
>>   
>  **Information you can access**
>> 
>> Examples of information you can access easily at MOCpages.com include personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications preferences, and other settings); e-mail notification settings; the "Your Account" area (including your reviews, votes, and personal profile); all of the content that you have personally created (including your MOC's pages, your home page, links to images, and links to other sites.) 

 |  |  |  | 

MOCpages is an unofficial, fan-created web service that is not sponsored by [](http://www.lego.com/).   
©2002-2007 [](http://www.seankenney.com/).  |
